let json_data = 
{"questions": [{"question": "____________________ is a disease caused by the inability to properly metabolize glucose due to insulin insufficiency or insulin resistance.", "answers": ["Diabetes hepaticus", "Diabetes pernicious", "Diabetes insipidus", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Diabetes insipidus"]}, {"question": "Which of the following is true regarding monitoring glycemic control in diabetic patients?", "answers": ["There is currently no mechanism for assessing long-term glycemic control is this population.", "Measuring the levels of glucose in the patient\u2019s bloodstream provides information about his/her long-term glycemic control.", "Measuring the levels of glucose in the patient\u2019s urine provides information about his/her long-term glycemic control.", "Long-term glycemic control is best assessed by measuring levels of glycosylated hemoglobin in the patient\u2019s blood."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Measuring the levels of glucose in the patient\u2019s bloodstream provides information about his/her long-term glycemic control."]}, {"question": "When oxygen is not available ____________________________________.", "answers": ["only fat metabolism can be used to generate ATP", "glycolysis occurs and the pyruvate formed is converted to lactate and handled by the Cori cycle", "glycolysis cannot occur", "glycolysis occurs and the pyruvate formed is converted to acetyl CoA, which enters Kreb\u2019s cycle"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "In ______________________________, an inorganic phosphate is added to ADP to form ATP.", "answers": ["transphosphorylation", "oxidative phosphorylation", "autophosphorylation", "substrate-level phosphorylation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["substrate-level phosphorylation"]}, {"question": "How many molecules of ATP can be formed by oxidative phosphorylation from each molecule of reduced FAD (FADH2) that feeds a pair of electrons to the electron transport chain?", "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Diabetes mellitus is associated with ____________________________.", "answers": ["deficient ADH", "high blood glucose", "excessive insulin", "deficient glucagon"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["deficient glucagon"]}, {"question": "Anabolism would include which of the following processes?", "answers": ["conversion of nucleic acids to nucleotides", "conversion of protein to amino acids", "conversion of glucose to glycogen", "conversion of triglycerides to glycerol and fatty acids"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["conversion of protein to amino acids"]}, {"question": "Glycogen is stored in skeletal muscle and must be converted to ____________ before it can be used to generate energy (ATP).", "answers": ["acetate", "fructose", "glucose", "fat"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "__________________ is characterized by symptoms of polyuria [excessive urination], polydipsia [excessive water drinking], polyphagia [excessive eating], blindness, and neuropathy.", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Diabetes mellitus", "Parkinson's disease", "Hyperthyroidism"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "In _______________________________, a phosphate group is removed from an organic molecule to which it was attached and transferred to a molecule of ADP to form ATP.", "answers": ["co-phosphorylation", "substrate-level phosphorylation", "oxidative phosphorylation", "transphosphorylation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["oxidative phosphorylation"]}, {"question": "Pizza contains the following: 30 grams of carbohydrate, 50 grams of protein and 10 grams of fat. The calorie content of carbohydrate, protein and fat is 4, 4, and 9 Kcal/gram, respectively. How many calories (Kcal) does this pizza contain?", "answers": ["17", "41", "426", "410"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "If you compared 1 gram of each of the following, which one would contain the highest number of calories?", "answers": ["carbohydrate", "water", "fat", "alcohol"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["alcohol"]}, {"question": "When there is an abundance of glucose in one's bloodstream as the result of a recently ingested meal, the normal person is in _________________________.", "answers": ["the post-absorptive state, characterized by high blood glucagon and low blood insulin levels", "the absorptive state, characterized by high blood glucagon and low blood insulin levels", "the absorptive state, characterized by high blood insulin and low blood glucagon levels", "the post-absorptive state, characterized by high blood insulin and low blood glucagon levels"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["the absorptive state, characterized by high blood glucagon and low blood insulin levels"]}, {"question": "Which of the sub-cellular organelles listed below contains the electron transport chain and serves as the major site for ATP production, via oxidative phosphorylation, in the cell?", "answers": ["centrioles", "lysosomes", "ribosomes", "mitochondria"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Type 2 diabetes mellitus ________________.", "answers": ["is more common than type 1 diabetes mellitus", "is generally preceded by weight loss", "historically, occurs more frequently in young people than in older individuals", "always requires treatment with insulin injections"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "From each molecule of reduced FAD (FADH2) that feeds electrons to the electron transport chain in the mitochondria, _________________________.", "answers": ["2 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation", "2 molecules of ATP are formed by oxidative phosphorylation", "3 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation", "3 moleculs of ATP are formed by oxidative phosphorylation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["2 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation"]}, {"question": "Insulin stimulates _______________________________________.", "answers": ["anabolic reactions such as the breakdown of glycogen to glucose, and the breakdown of proteins into amino acids", "anabolic reactions such as the formation of glycogen from glucose and the formation of proteins from amino acids", "catabolic reactions such as the breakdown of glycogen to glucose and the breakdown of protein into amino acids", "catabolic reactions such as the formation of glycogen from glucose and protein from amino acids"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["anabolic reactions such as the breakdown of glycogen to glucose, and the breakdown of proteins into amino acids"]}, {"question": "For long-term storage, the body will preferentially store its reserves as ________________ because, on a gram per gram basis, when metabolized, this class of macromolecule provides the most energy to the body.", "answers": ["fat", "carbohydrate", "nucleic acid", "protein"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "When the body is at rest, skeletal muscle derives most of its energy ___________.", "answers": ["by metabolizing fats and using the free fatty acids from triglycerides for energy production", "by picking up and metabolizing glucose from the bloodstream", "by transferring phosphates from creatine phosphate to ADP", "by forming glucose from non carbohydrate sources and then metabolizing it"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["by forming glucose from non carbohydrate sources and then metabolizing it"]}, {"question": "When glycolysis occurs under aerobic conditions (i.e. when oxygen is present), the NADH formed in the cytosol can be used to generate additional ATP by oxidative phosphorylation. Which of the following statements is most accurate?", "answers": ["Cells in the liver and heart produce more ATP from this cytoplasmic NADH than other cells in the body.", "Cells in the liver and heart produce less ATP from this cytoplamsic NADH than other cells in the body.", "All cells in the body produce similar amounts of ATP from this cytoplamsic NADH."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Cells in the liver and heart produce less ATP from this cytoplamsic NADH than other cells in the body."]}, {"question": "Assessing a diabetic patient\u2019s long-term glycemic control is best achieved by measuring the amount of _______________ in his/her plasma.", "answers": ["glucose", "insulin", "glycosylated hemoglobin", "C-peptide"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["glucose"]}, {"question": "Which of the following molecules serves as the body\u2019s \u2018energy currency\u2019 \u2013 i.e. is the molecule the body relies on to provide the energy needed to drive energy-dependent processes?", "answers": ["ADH", "ATP", "FSH", "DNA"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true for aerobic metabolism of sugars?", "answers": ["During aerobic metabolism, 1 molecule of glucose is converted to 2 molecules of lactic acid.", "Aerobic metabolism of glucose occurs in the cytoplasm of the cell.", "Aerobic metabolism of glucose does not require oxygen.", "Aerobic metabolism of glucose generates more ATP than anaerobic metabolism of glucose."], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "In non heart/non liver cells, if glycolysis occurs in the presence of oxygen, it generates a gross gain of __________________.", "answers": ["8 ATP molecules \u2013 2 by substrate-level phosphorylation and 6 by oxidative phosphorylation", "8 ATP molecules; 4 by substrate-level phosphorylation, and 4 by oxidative phosphorylation", "10 ATP molecules; 4 by substrate-level phosphorylation and 6 by oxidative phosphorylation", "10 ATP molecules \u2013 6 by substrate-level phosphorylation and 4 by oxidative phosphorylation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["8 ATP molecules \u2013 2 by substrate-level phosphorylation and 6 by oxidative phosphorylation"]}, {"question": "Which of the following statements about glycolysis is correct?", "answers": ["Glycolysis occurs in the cytosol, but only if oxygen is available.", "Glycolysis occurs in the cytosol in the presence or absence of oxygen.", "Glycolysis is the metabolic pathway used to transport lactate from skeletal muscle cells to the liver.", "Glycolysis occurs in the mitochondria."], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Substrate-level phosphorylation of ADP to produce ATP ___________________.", "answers": ["involves the transfer of a phosphate group from an organic molecule to ADP", "occurs in glycolysis but not in the Kreb's cycle", "is the primary mechanism for generating most of the cell's ATP during aerobic or anaerobic conditions", "involves the addition of an inorganic phosphate group to ADP"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["involves the addition of an inorganic phosphate group to ADP"]}, {"question": "________________________ is the formation of glucose from non-carbohydrate sources.", "answers": ["Glycogenolysis", "Gluconeogenesis"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Most of the body's ATP is produced by _______________________.", "answers": ["glycolysis, which occurs in the cytosol", "oxidative phosphorylation, which occurs in the mitochondria", "oxidative phosphorylation, which occurs in the cytosol", "glycolysis, which occurs in the mitochondria"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["glycolysis, which occurs in the cytosol"]}, {"question": "For every molecule of glucose metabolized in the presence of oxygen using glycolysis, the Kreb's cycle, and the electron transport chain, theoretically, __________ molecules of ATP can be generated.", "answers": ["~6", "~10", "~24", "~36"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["~10"]}, {"question": "Measuring the amount of glycolsylated hemoglobin in the blood is a useful tool for monitoring a diabetic patient\u2019s glycemic control (how well the patient has managed to control his/her plasma glucose levels) in the past _______________.", "answers": ["2-3 months", "24 hours", "week", "8 hours"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Free radicals can cause tissue damage, especially to nucleic acids and cell membranes. By neutralizing free radicals or converting them to less reactive substances, __________________, like vitamins A and C, or glutathione, lessen the damage otherwise caused by these unstable, reactive molecules.", "answers": ["enzymes", "retroradicals", "antioxidants", "cytochromes"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Compared to other organs in the body, the liver and the heart can generate slightly higher amounts of ATP per molecule of glucose they metabolize aerobically, because _____________________________.", "answers": ["they pass the electrons from cytoplasmic FAD to mitochondrial NAD", "they pass the electrons from cytoplasmic NAD to mitochondrial FAD", "they pass the electrons from cytoplasmic NAD to mitochondrial NAD", "they pass the electrons from cytoplasmic FAD to mitochondrial FAD"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["they pass the electrons from cytoplasmic NAD to mitochondrial FAD"]}, {"question": "When non liver and non heart cells metabolize a molecule of glucose in the absence of oxygen, the 2 molecules of reduced NAD that form in the cytoplasm will generate _____________ molecules of ATP by oxidative phosphorylation in the electron transport chain.", "answers": ["4", "0", "2", "6"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["4"]}, {"question": "Which of the following statements regarding glycolysis is true?", "answers": ["Glycolysis is an anaerobic metabolic process that occurs in the cytosol and converts glucose to pyruvate.", "Glycolysis is an aerobic metabolic process that occurs in the mitochondria and converts glucose to pyruvate.", "Glycolysis is an aerobic metabolic process that occurs in the cytosol and converts glucose to pyruvate.", "Glycolysis is an anaerobic metabolic process that occurs in the mitochondria and converts glucose to pyruvate."], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "When you are in the absorptive state (immediately after a meal), which hormone is more active due to high blood sugar?", "answers": ["insulin", "glucagon"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["glucagon"]}, {"question": "Acetoacetic acid, ", "answers": ["free radicals", "ketones", "reactive oxygen species", "antioxidants"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "__________________ is a protein molecule, produced in adipose (fat) cells, that feeds back to the brain's satiety center in the hypothalamus and through negative feedback regulates food intake and body weight.", "answers": ["Lipostatin", "Insulin", "Leptin", "Glucagon"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "When liver and heart cells metabolize a molecule of glucose in the presence of oxygen, the 2 molecules of reduced NAD that form in the cytoplasm during glycolysis will generate _____________ molecules of ATP by oxidative phosphorylation in the electron transport chain.", "answers": ["4", "0", "6", "2"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "When you are in the post-absorptive state (&gt;4 hours after a meal), which hormone is more active due to low blood sugar?", "answers": ["glucagon", "insulin"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["insulin"]}, {"question": "For every molecule of glucose that is metabolized in the presence of oxygen, how many revolutions of Kreb\u2019s cycle will occur?", "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "At rest, in the absence of stress and exercise, skeletal muscle gains most of its energy via ____________________________.", "answers": ["metabolism of glycogen", "metabolism of blood glucose", "metabolism of amino acids from proteins", "metabolism of fatty acids from triglycerides"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["metabolism of blood glucose"]}, {"question": "Many cells use glucose transport proteins to move glucose into the cell.&nbsp; Cells in which of the following tissues use GLUT4 glucose transporters that are inserted into the cells\u2019 plasma membranes in response to insulin?", "answers": ["liver and adipose", "skeletal muscle and adipose", "brain and gonads", "kidney and blood vessels"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["liver and adipose"]}, {"question": "Which of the following statements regarding the breakdown of glucose to carbon dioxide and water is true?", "answers": ["This process generates only enough ATP to provide energy for the reactions involved, but does not generate additional ATP that the body can use to drive other cellular processes.", "The cell uses a step-wise cascade of chemical reactions that will generate ATP, but minimize heat production, so as not to destroy the cell.", "This process generates no ATP. ATP is absorbed in the intestine from foodstuffs that have been ingested and digested.", "The cell breaks down glucose to carbon dioxide and water in a single-step reaction that generates a lot of heat and ATP simultaneously."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["This process generates only enough ATP to provide energy for the reactions involved, but does not generate additional ATP that the body can use to drive other cellular processes."]}, {"question": "___________________ reactions are metabolic reactions that require energy input to synthesize macromolecules from simpler precursor molecules.", "answers": ["Anabolic", "Catabolic", "Formative", "Creative"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Catabolic"]}, {"question": "The metabolic pathway involving transport (via the bloodstream) of lactate from muscle to the liver, conversion of lactate into glucose within the liver, and return transport of glucose from the liver back to muscle (via the bloodstream) is called ___________________.", "answers": ["the actate transport cycle (LTC)", "glycolysis", "electron transport", "the Cori cycle"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "If you compared 1 gram of each of the following, which one would contain the lowest number of calories?", "answers": ["water", "fat", "alcohol", "carbohydrate"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "________________ is the hormone that is secreted by fat cells and acts, via negative feedback in the hypothalamus, to regulate long-term food consumption and fat accumulation.", "answers": ["Leptin", "Insulin", "Actin", "Reductin"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "When non liver and non heart cells metabolize a molecule of glucose in the presence of oxygen, the 2 molecules of reduced NAD that form in the cytoplasm during glycolysis will generate _____________ molecules of ATP by oxidative phosphorylation in the electron transport chain.", "answers": ["2", "6", "0", "4"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["6"]}, {"question": "At rest, _______________________________________.", "answers": ["the brain uses the majority of glucose in the blood, while the other tissues in the body metabolize fatty acids for their energy production", "the brain and other body tissues remove and use roughly equal amounts of glucose from the bloodstream to produce the energy they need", "the brain metabolizes fatty acids to generate the energy it needs, leaving the glucose in the bloodstream to be used by the other tissues of the body for their energy production needs", "all the tissues of the body, including the brain, metabolize fatty acids to generate the energy they need, saving the glucose in the blood to be used only during periods of intense exercise"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["the brain metabolizes fatty acids to generate the energy it needs, leaving the glucose in the bloodstream to be used by the other tissues of the body for their energy production needs"]}, {"question": "Which of the following statements about insulin is correct?", "answers": ["Insulin is secreted from the alpha cells of the pancreas in response to high blood glucose levels.", "Insulin is secreted from the alpha cells of the pancreas in response to low blood glucose levels.", "Insulin is secreted from the beta cells of the pancreas in response to high blood glucose levels.", "Insulin is secreted from the beta cells of the pancreas in response to low blood glucose levels."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Insulin is secreted from the beta cells of the pancreas in response to low blood glucose levels."]}, {"question": "Molecules produced by natural metabolic processes, or due to the effects of cigarettes, pollutants, UV irradiation, etc., that contain unpaired electrons and cause damage to proteins, cell membranes, and nucleic acids and are thought to influence the aging process are called ___________________.", "answers": ["expensive radicals", "free ridicules", "free radicals", "militant molecules"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Catabolism would include which of the following processes?", "answers": ["conversion of nucleotides into nucleic acids", "conversion of protein to amino acids", "conversion of glucose to glycogen", "conversion of glycerol and fatty acids to triglyceride"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["conversion of glucose to glycogen"]}, {"question": "Insulin is produced in and released by the __________________________.", "answers": ["thyroid gland", "adrenal cortex", "pancreas", "pituitary"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "_____________________ reactions are metabolic reactions that break down complex macromolecules to elementary units, releasing energy in the process.", "answers": ["Anabolic", "Degradation", "Catabolic", "Degenerative"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "One gram of protein contains _________.", "answers": ["more calories than a gram of carbohydrate", "the same number of calories as a gram of fat", "fewer calories than a gram of fat", "more calories than a gram of alcohol (ethanol)"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Glucagon is secreted by the ___________________.", "answers": ["pancreas", "anterior pituitary", "liver", "adrenal cortex"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Which of the following is true about the post-absorptive state?", "answers": ["During the post-absorptive state, the alpha cells in the pancreas are more active than the beta cells.", "The post-absorptive state occurs immediately after ingestion of a meal.", "During the post-absorptive state, there are high levels of glucose in the bloodstream.", "During the post-absorptive state, the predominant pancreatic hormone in the bloodstream stimulates anabolic reactions in its target tissues."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["During the post-absorptive state, the predominant pancreatic hormone in the bloodstream stimulates anabolic reactions in its target tissues."]}, {"question": "Which of the following statements about glucagon is correct?", "answers": ["Glucagon is secreted from the beta cells of the pancreas in response to low blood glucose levels.", "Glucagon is secreted from the beta cells of the pancreas in response to high blood glucose levels.", "Glucagon is secreted from the alpha cells of the pancreas in response to high blood glucose levels.", "Glucagon is secreted from the alpha cells of the pancreas in response to low blood glucose levels."], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "From each molecule of reduced NAD (NADH) that feeds electrons to the electron transport chain in the mitochondria, ___________________.", "answers": ["3 molecules of ATP are formed by oxidative phosphorylation", "3 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation", "2 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation", "2 molecules of ATP are formed by oxidative phosphorylation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["2 molecules of ATP are formed by substrate-level phosphorylation"]}, {"question": "Axons are considered the \u201cexcitable\u201d region of the cell because they contain _________________ that, when activated, result in generation of action potentials.", "answers": ["ritalin-activated ion channels", "ligand-gated ion channels", "hyperactive ion channels", "voltage-gated ion channels"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["ritalin-activated ion channels"]}, {"question": "The Na+/K+ ATPase pumps simultaneously transport _____________________________.", "answers": ["3 Na+ and 3 K+ into the cell", "2 Na+ into and 3 K+ out of the cell", "3 Na+ and 3 K+ out of the cell", "3 Na+ out and 2 K+ into the cell"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["3 Na+ and 3 K+ into the cell"]}, {"question": "Use the ", "answers": ["<strong>e</strong>xit from", "enter at"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Sensory neurons can be differentiated from motor neurons by their lack of _______________.", "answers": ["axons", "cell bodies", "true anatomic dendrites <br>", "nuclei"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["nuclei"]}, {"question": "Which of the neurons listed fit the following criteria: 1)are also known as efferent fibers; 2)carry information from the CNS to skeletal muscle that&nbsp;is under voluntary control; and 3) possess true anatomic dendrites projecting from their cell bodies?", "answers": ["sensory fibers of the PNS", "somatic motor fibers of the PNS", "autonomic motor fibers of the PNS", "all neurons in the human body"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["autonomic motor fibers of the PNS"]}, {"question": "Which of the neurons listed below would conduct electrochemical impulses the slowest?", "answers": ["a wide-diameter, myelinated neuron", "a narrow-diameter, myelinated neuron", "a wide-diameter, unmyelinated neuron", "a narrow-diameter, unmyelinated neuron"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["a wide-diameter, myelinated neuron"]}, {"question": "Which of the following are true of graded potentials?", "answers": ["they travel along the neuron\u2019s plasma membrane, away from their site of origin, without any decrease in magnitude", "they occur primarily in the axon region of the neuron", "as they travel away from their site of origin on the neuron\u2019s plasma they weaken in magnitude", "they occur along the entire surface of the neuron"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Which of the following situations would cause the nerve cell to hyperpolarize?", "answers": ["decreased flow of potassium ions out of the nerve cell", "increased flow of sodium ions into the nerve cell", "decreased flow of chloride ions into the nerve cell", "increased flow of potassium ions out of the nerve cell"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["decreased flow of potassium ions out of the nerve cell"]}, {"question": "Question options:", "answers": ["________________ takes place when MANY pre-synaptic neurons synapse and convey impulses to a SINGLE postsynaptic neuron.", "Facilitation", "Convergence", "Divergence", "Summation"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Divergence"]}, {"question": "___________________ is a chemical substance that is similar enough in structure to acetylcholine it can bind to acetylcholine receptors on the motor end plate, but cannot depolarize the cell when it does bind the receptors, so causes flaccid muscle paralysis.", "answers": ["Phosphocholine", "Botulinum toxin", "Curare", "Bordatella toxin"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["Phosphocholine"]}, {"question": "The resting membrane potential of an unstimulated nerve cell is approximately _______________________.", "answers": ["-10 mV", "-70 mV", "+70 mV", "+10 mV"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Electrolytes are non metallic ions in your bloodstream.&nbsp; A number of electrolytes can affect proper conduction of electrical impulses (action potentials) in the nervous system. Which of the following electrolytes play the most important role in nerve function i.e. in the nerve cell\u2019s ability to generate an action potential?", "answers": ["iron and calcium", "magnesium and sulfate", "iron and chloride", "sodium and potassium"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["iron and chloride"]}, {"question": "Efferent neurons _________________________________.", "answers": ["are part of the motor portion of the peripheral nervous system that carry information from the central nervous system to the body", "are part of the sensory portion of the peripheral nervous system that carry information from the body to the central nervous system", "are part of the motor portion of the peripheral nervous system that carry information from the body to the central nervous system", "are part of the sensory portion of the peripheral nervous system that carry information from the central nervous system to the body"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["are part of the motor portion of the peripheral nervous system that carry information from the body to the central nervous system"]}, {"question": "The Na+/K+ ATPase pumps in the cell membrane contribute to the development and maintenance of the neuron's resting membrane potential because simultaneously they ______________________________.", "answers": ["pump 3 sodium ions into the cell and 2 potassium ions out of the cell", "pump 3 sodium ions out of the cell and 2 potassium ions into the cell", "pump 3 sodium ions out of the cell and 3 potassium ions into the cell", "pump 3 sodium ions into the cell and 3 potassium ions out of the cell"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "Which of the following tissues is/are considered \u201cexcitable\u201d?", "answers": ["muscle and connective", "epithelial &amp; neural", "neural only", "muscle and neural"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["epithelial &amp; neural"]}, {"question": "In the process of repolarization, the membrane potential in a depolarized cell becomes more negative, eventually returning to the resting membrane potential, because _________________________________.", "answers": ["Na+ influx stops and K+ influx begins", "K+ influx stops and Na+ efflux begins", "K+ influx stops and Na+ influx begins", "Na+ influx stops and K+ efflux begins"], "correct": "", "incorrect": []}, {"question": "The myelin sheath that surrounds the axons of some nerve cells is composed of _____________.", "answers": ["protein", "nucleic acids", "fat", "carbohydrates"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["nucleic acids"]}, {"question": "The plasma membrane can regulate passage of ionized (charged) particles into and out of the cell, creating intracellular fluids that differ considerably from extracellular fluids with respect to ion composition. Which statement below regarding the composition of the intra- and extracellular fluids is correct?", "answers": ["The chloride (Cl-) concentration is greater inside the cell than outside the cell.", "The sodium (Na+) concentration is greater inside the cell than outside the cell.", "The potassium (K+) concentration is greater inside the cell than outside the cell.", "The concentration of both sodium (Na+) and potassium (K+) is greater outside the cell than inside the cell."], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["The sodium (Na+) concentration is greater inside the cell than outside the cell."]}, {"question": "EPSP, IPSP, and motor end plate potentials are all examples of ________________ potentials, thus they all ________________ as they migrate away from their sites of origin.", "answers": ["action / do not decrease in magnitude", "graded / do not decrease in magnitude", "action / decrease in magnitude", "graded / decrease in magnitude"], "correct": "", "incorrect": ["graded / do not decrease in magnitude"]}]}
    








let question_array = json_data["questions"];


let ssearch = function(term) {
    for (let q of question_array) {
        if (q["question"].indexOf(term) > -1) {
            if (q["correct"].length > 0) {
                console.log("Question: ")
                console.log(q["question"])
                console.log("Correct answer: ")
                console.log(q["correct"])
            }
            else if(q["incorrect"].length > 0){
                console.log("Question: ")
                console.log(q["question"])
                console.log("Incorrect answer(s): ")
                for (let a of q["incorrect"]) {
                    console.log(a);
                }
            }
        }
    }
}
